# Soheila Sadeghian

Email: soheila.sadeghian89@gmail.com

Phone: +989128481421

Website: https://soheilasadeghian.github.io Github: https://github.com/soheilasadeghian

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/soheilasadeghian

I'm a web developer with 6+ years of experience who is completely passionate about encountering new challenges.

My skills run the full range of development activities from requirements gathering through testing and implementation.

I am reliable, flexible, adaptable, fast learner and i have experience working with teams which means i can hit the ground running.

I am a self-discipline and i can be left alone to complete tasks quickly, diligently and on time.

## **Work Experiences**

## Carboy Oct 2018 - Dec 2019

#### Full Stack Web Developer

The carboy (http://carboy.ir) is the first application in Tehran that anyone can reserve online services for a car. I designed, developed, and maintained the back-end using ASP.NET(C#) MVC and SQL. improved code quality and system performance.

*Carboy System*: With Carboy's application, you just need to specify the location of your car, type of service, vehicle model, the preferred time and submit your request till the Carboy team reaches your location at the specified time.

Github: https://github.com/soheilasadeghian/Carboy

#### CallWithMe Jul 2017 – Aug 2018

#### Midd-Level Web Developer

Designing and launching all kinds of websites with special and different designs. Good knowledge of C# oop and transferred new tips to teammates. woked in Git and TFS for source control. some project i did in this company with our team:

- Appinno: News website with admin panel used WebService(SOAP). I designed and added new modules and features like a notification system. Github: https://github.com/soheilasadeghian/Carboy
- HamiDiabet: WebSite to provide services to diabetic patients (Website & API Project with JWT Authentication)
  Github: https://github.com/soheilasadeghian/HamiDiabet
- *LMS*: Website for selling learning packages with Zarinpal payment gateway and a management panel Github: https://github.com/soheilasadeghian/LMS
- CallWithMe: Company Website Profile for CallWithMe company Github: https://github.com/soheilasadeghian/callwithme

## JeihoonPublication Jan 2015 - June 2016

### Junior Web Developer

Jeihoon: Jeihoon Online Book Shopping. website link: http://jeihoon.net/

Shaya: Company Website Profile for shaya-solutions company. Github: https://github.com/soheilasadeghian/shaya

## IRAN University of Medical Sciences (IUMS) May 2014 – Dec 2014

#### Junior Web Developer

*Triage System*: designing and developing the front-end and back-end triage system for 7tir hospital. Implemented responsive designs, ensuring a seamless user experience across all devices.

## Sanjesh Afzar Asia(SAA) Jul 2012 – Apr 2014

#### Software Support

Support for softwares and hardwares produced through customer communication and CRM application. Worked closely with clients to gather requirements and provide ongoing technical support.

### Skills

Server-side programming: Strong knowledge in C# , .NET, ASP.Net, MVC, PHP, Laravel

Database: SQL, MySql

Client-side programming: Javascript, Jquery, TypeScript, Reactjs

Web User Interface: HTML, CSS3, Bootstrap

Source Controls: Git,TFS API technology: RestApi

Learning: ReactJs, NodeJs, DevOps

## **EDUCATION**